Capital Area School Development Association; Records apap065
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Reports and Publications, 1950-1994; 2; 3 cubic ft.
  - Survey of the Elementary School Building Needs Mechanicville, 1954 (Box 1 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 38)
  - Conference Leadership, 1955 (Box 1 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 39)
  - Custodial Training for Health and Safety in Schools, 1955 (Box 1 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 40)
  - Program in Off-Campus Student Teaching-Handbook, 1955 (Box 1 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 41)
  - Selecting a Teacher's Career, ca. 1955 (Box 1 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 42)
  - The Role of the Custodian in the Total School Program, 1956 (Box 1 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 43)
  - What is the Future of Higher Education, 1956 (Box 1 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 44)
  - What the People of Carman Think About Their Schools, 1956 (Box 1 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 45)
  - What Scotia-Glenville People Think About Their Schools, 1956 (Box 1 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 46)
  - What the People of Schenectady Think About Their Schools, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 47)
  - Salaries and Salary Policies of CASDA Schools, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 48)
  - Salaries and Salary Policies of CASDA Schools, 1956-1957 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 1)
  - Salaries for School Personnel, 1957 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 2)
  - Independent Learning Activities, 1958 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 3)
  - The Function of Secondary Education in American Society, 1958 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 4)
  - Salaries and Salary Policies of CASDA Schools, 1958-1959 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 5)
  - An Apple for the First-Year Teacher, 1959 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 6)
  - Language Arts A Sequential Program, 1959; copy 2 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 7)
  - Language Arts A Sequential Program, 1959; copy 1 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 8)
  - A Decade of Progress and A Look Ahead, 1960 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 9)
  - Foreign Language: A Selected Bibliography for the Elementary School, 1960 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 10)
  - Learning For Adjustment Pupil Handbook, 1960 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 11)
  - Modern Building and Classrooms for Modern Times, 1960 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 12)
  - Pupil Experiences in the Elementary Science, 1960 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 13)
  - Salaries and Salary Policies of CASDA Schools, 1960-1961; 1960 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 14)
  - Salaries and Salary Policies of CASDA Schools, 1959-1960; 1960 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 15)
  - Seminar: Summary Report of the Third Administrative Seminar, 1959-1960; 1960 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 16)
  - The Auditing of School Records, 1961 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 17)
  - Developing a Quality Educational Program, 1961 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 18)
  - Maintaining a Good Learning Environment through Proper Custodial Service, 1961 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 19)
  - Salaries and Salary Policies of CASDA Schools, 1961-1962; 1961 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 20)
  - The School Business Official in New York State, 1961 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 21)
  - Custodianship: The Man and the Job, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 22)
  - The Junior High School and the Adolescent, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 23)
  - The School Secretary as a Professional, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 24)
  - Survey of Reading Practices in CASDA Secondary Schools, 1961-1962; 1962 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 25)
  - Collective Bargaining and the Teacher, 1963 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 26)
  - Communication: A Selected, Annotated Bibliography, 1960-1961 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 27)
  - Communication: A Selected, Annotated Bibliography, Revised, 1963-1964 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 27)
  - East Greenbush Central School Grievance Procedures, 1963 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 28)
  - On the Move in Reading, 1963 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 29)
  - Operation and Maintenance Handbook, Electricity, 1963 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 30)
  - Operations and Maintenance: Trends and Processes, 1963 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 31)
  - The Educational Secretaries Conference Notebook, 1964 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 32)
  - Operations and Maintenance Handbook, Small Gasoline Engines, 1964 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 33)
  - Quest for the Creative: Analytical Report of a Seminar in Creative Music and the Related Arts for Elementary School Children, 1964 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 34)
  - Salaries and Salary Policies of CASDA Schools, 1964-1965; 1964 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 35)
  - The School Board as a Political Force, 1964 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 36)
  - School Finance as a Social Investment, 1964 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 37)
  - Sourcebook for Mathematics Teachers, 1964 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 38)
  - Communications: A Selected Annotated Bibliography, ca. 1965 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 39)
  - Decision-Making: A Selected, Annotated Bibliography, ca. 1965 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 40)
  - Delegation: A Selected, Annotated Bibliography, ca. 1965 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 41)
  - Dissemination of Educational Research, 1965 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 42)
  - Education-The Next Five Years, 1965 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 43)
  - The Educational Secretaries' Conference Notebook, 1965 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 44)
  - How Much Psychology in School Counseling, 1965 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 45)
  - Innovation: A Selected Annotated Bibliography, ca. 1965 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 46)
  - Operations and Maintenance Handbook, Basic Machines, 1965 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 47)
  - Organization: A Selected Annotated Bibliography, ca. 1965 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 48)
  - Salaries and Salary Policies of CASDA Schools, 1965-1966; 1965 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 49)
  - Staff and Service: A Special Study of Personnel Needs in the Scotia-Glenville Public Schools, 1965 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 50)
  - Educational Costs in CASDA Schools for 1964-1965, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 51)
  - The Educational Secretaries' Conference Notebook, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 52)
  - Labor Relations in Public Education, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 53)
  - New Vectors in School Finance, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 54)
  - On the Move in Elementary Reading, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 55)
  - Salaries and Salary Policies of CASDA Schools, 1966-1967; 1966 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 56)
  - The School Business Official in New York State Status and Trend, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 57)
  - Teachers Aids, a Selected Bibliography, ca. 1966 (Box 2 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 58)
  - CASDA Profile of Member School Districts, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 1)
  - Let's Get Organized: Selected Presentations from the Educational Secretaries Conference, 1967 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 2)
  - Operations and Maintenance Handbook, Lawn Establishment and Maintenance, 1967 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 3)
  - Salaries and Salary Policies of CASDA Schools, 1967-1968; 1967 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 4)
  - Selected Bibliography on Grouping, 1967 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 5)
  - Selected Bibliography on Teacher Aids, ca. 1967 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 6)
  - Suggested Materials and Resources: Social Problems that Affect Development of School Program, 1967 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 7)
  - Questions Concerning HPER Programs, 1967 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 8)
  - Who Makes School Policy in the United States, 1967 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 9)
  - Attitudes, Theories, and Techniques in Collective Negations in Education, A Selected Annotated Bibliography, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 10)
  - CASDA Profile of School Districts, 1968-1969; 1968 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 11)
  - Financing American Schools in the Years Ahead, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 12)
  - Independent Learning Activities, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 13)
  - Report Civil Disorders Commission, Religions Leader, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 14)
  - Salaries and Salary Policies of CASDA Schools, 1968-1969; 1968 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 15)
  - The Board's Man in the Negotiation Process, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 16)
  - Status Study of Capital Area District Boards of Cooperative Education Services, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 17)
  - Status Study of Capital Area Boards of Cooperative Educational Services, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 18)
  - Operations and Maintenance Handbook, Characteristics of Wood, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 19)
  - Tape Recorded Conference Speeches, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 20)
  - You Are CASDA, ca. 1968 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 21)
  - Capital Area School Business Management Study Group, Program Workshop, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 22)
  - CASDA Research Needs Survey, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 23)
  - CASDA Survey-Current Individual School District Research Projects, 1968-1969; 1969 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 24)
  - Class Size, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 25)
    Bibliography.
  - Educational Research the Learning Process and School Policy Making, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 26)
  - Salaries and Salary Policies of CASDA Schools, 1969-1970; 1969 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 27)
  - Schools and their Responsibilities for Human Rights, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 28)
  - Tape Recorded Speeches, An Annotated List, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 29)
  - Value Engineering as a Decision Making Tool, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 30)
  - The Non-graded School, a Selected Annotated Bibliography, 1970 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 31)
  - Reading Instruction: A Selected Annotated Bibliography, 1970 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 32)
  - Status Study of Services for Children with Learning Disabilities in Columbia and Green Counties, 1969-1970; 1970 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 33)
  - Salaries and Finance Data of CASDA Schools, 1970-1971; 1971 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 34)
  - Salaries and Finance Data of CASDA Schools, 1971-1972; 1971 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 35)
  - Teaching Aids in Consumer Economics, 1970-1971 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 36)
  - CASDA Program Development Survey, 1972 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 37)
  - Review of the Resource Management Functions of the Scotia-Glenville Central School District, 1972 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 38)
  - Salaries and Finance Data of CASDA Schools, 1972-1973; 1972 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 39)
  - Alcohol-Drugs-Tobacco: Teacher's Source Book and Guide, 1973 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 40)
  - Directory of School Personnel for CASDA Area Schools, 1973 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 41)
  - Salaries and Finance Data of CASDA Schools, 1973-1974; 1973 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 42)
  - A Competency-Based Guide and Directive for Off-Campus Student Teachers in Secondary English, Mathematics, Social Sciences, 1974 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 43)
  - Teacher Education Developmental Service Catalog of Holdings, 1975 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 44)
  - Competency-Based Teacher Education Program: Natural Sciences, 1976 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 45)
  - A Handbook, Guide, and Directive for Off-Campus Student Teachers, 1976 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 46)
  - Statistical and Financial Study of CASDA Schools, 1975-1976 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 47)
    Including BOCES Supplement, 1976.
  - A Teaching Guide for use in Connection with Reversible Lane Signalization, A Case Study in Benefit-Cost Analysis, 1977 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 48)
  - Exemplary Practices Report from Project Super Teach, 1981 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 49)
  - Cross Training for Teachers and Specialist Educators in Special Education, Occupational and Continuing Education, Vocational Rehabilitation Guidance Report, 1981 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 50)
  - Cross Training for Teachers and Specialist Educators in Special Education Occupational and Continuing Education, Vocational Rehabilitation, Proceedings, 1981 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 51)
  - In-service Education Project for Industrial Arts Teachers "Project 'Super' Teach", 1981 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 52)
  - Report on Instructional Use of Computers in the Public Schools in the Capital District, 1981 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 53)
  - Statistical and Financial Study of CASDA Schools, 1982-1983; 1982 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 54)
  - Statistical and Financial Study of CASDA Schools, 1983-1984; 1983 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 55)
  - Supply and Demand Problems in Teaching, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 56)
  - Capital District Task Force on Aging-Out, ca. 1985 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 57)
  - Teaching Math/Science Concepts K-6 A Sampler of Classroom Tested Ideas, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 58)
  - Ninth Annual School Law Conference, 1994 July 19 (Box 3 (2-Reports and Publications), Folder 59)